Isn't downtime just the opposite of uptime?
停机时间与正常运行时间正好相反吗 ?
Why should we talk about it as a separate topic?
我们为什么要把它作为一个单独的话题来谈呢 ?
Downtime has some important caveats.
停机时间有一些重要的警告
Most platforms are not entirely within your control.
大多数平台并非完全在您的控制范围内
You might use third-parties for aspects of your platform,
您可能将第三方用于平台的各个方面
such as email delivery,
例如电子邮件传递
video streaming, data collection, and hosting.
视频流 数据收集和托管
Do any of these sound familiar?
这些听起来很熟悉吗
Certainly at a minimum,
当然至少
you know about AWS.
你知道 AWS 的事
What if AWS goes down?
如果 AWS 停机怎么办 ?
How can it be expected to account for all of these services?
如何能预计到所有这些服务 ?
You don't run them all yourself,
你自己都不做
so you can't personally keep them up and running.
所以你不能亲自让他们跑起来
What do you do? You can choose third parties who themselves provide SLAs.
你是做什么的 您可以选择自己提供 SLA的第三方
Then in your own contracts,
那就在你自己的合同里
you can specify that you only use third parties with a minimum SLA threshold,
您可以指定仅使用具有最低 SLA 阈值的第三方
but that you are not responsible for the third party downtime.
但你不会为第三方的宕机负责
Well, at least you can try.
至少你可以试试
Your customers may not accept that.
您的客户可能无法接受
This is where you turn the negotiators within
这就是你把谈判者变成
your organization to work out all of the details so that
你的组织把所有细节都拿出来
both parties and yourself understand what will and will not be your responsibilities.
双方和自己都明白什么会 也不会是你的责任
Let's talk about some math.
让我们谈谈数学
If you provide a 99.9 percent SLAs to your customers and
如果您向客户提供 99.9% SLA
your third parties all provide 99.9 percent SLAs to you,
你的第三方都给你提供了 99.9% 个 SLA
you should be covered, right?
你应该被掩盖了对吧
Only if all of that downtime completely overlaps.
仅当所有这些停机时间都完全重叠
If you happen to use all of your allotment of downtime in a month and even one of
如果您碰巧使用了一个月内的所有停机时间 甚至是其中一个
your third parties uses any of
你的第三方使用
their allotment and their downtime doesn't fall within your downtime,
他们的分配和停机时间不会在您的停机时间内
you just missed being up for 99.9 percent of the month.
你错过了 99.9% 个月的时间
Obviously, this problem just gets bigger as more third-parties that you use.
显然 这个问题比你使用的第三方更大
But doing away with third parties is likely not practical either.
但是 与第三方进行谈判也很可能是不实际的
So make sure you covered this case in writing in your agreements.
所以请确保您在协议中以书面形式覆盖此案例